YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
时间轴： godwuwen 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
翻译： Vero  非燕  猫王不要完结 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
校对： YY    后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第十四集
大家好  马修和莉莉去哪了
Hey, guys. Where are Marshall and Lily?
发生了件不幸的事
Something terrible happened.
他们没事吧  他们进医院了吗
Are they okay? Are they in the hospital?
没有
No.
那地方比医院还...糟糕得多
Somewhere much... much worse.
长岛
Long Island!
从今晚开始  我们就永居长岛啦
Tonight, we're moving out there for good.
十分钟前
是啊  给你们我们新家的钥匙
Yeah. Here are your spare keys to our new house.
长岛
Long Island?
我不明白
I don't understand.
你在这也能买到美黑喷雾啊
you can spray tans here.
长岛太阳辐射强  日照充足
年平均日照时间为2400到2800小时
我从来不愿相信这一天会真的到来
I never let myself believe this day would really come.
就好像《五口之家》再次被取消了
It's like when they canceled Party of Five for the second time.
《五口之家》美国青春剧  共六季
因收视率低第一季差点被取消  但却在1996年意外获得金球奖
第一次是他们取消...看比赛的时候
I mean when they... canceled sports.
各位  我们还会经常见面
Guys, we'll still see each other all the time,
经常打电话
and we'll talk on the phone.
我知道人人都说  有了孩子就意味着
And I know people say that having kids means
告别朋友  但是...
you won't see your friends anymore, but...
天啊  现在是道别  对吗
Oh, God, this is good-bye, isn't it?
好了  别这样
No. Stop it.
伙计们  这并无任何改变
Guys, this doesn't change anything.
我们离这儿只有四十六分钟的车程
We are only a 46-minute train ride away.
你们也随时可以来访
Just pop out whenever you want.
那...这里应该没人坐了吧
So... I guess this seat is open.
不  还会有的
No, it isn't.
我还是去搬把椅子吧
I'll go get a chair.
曲终人散
So that's it.
马修没了
No more Marshall.
莉莉没了
No more Lily.
他们都没了
They're gone.
这就意味着...
Which means...
再也没有扫兴的已婚夫妇
no lame married couple
把我所有的绝妙点子通通给否决掉
shooting down all my amazing ideas.
各位  好消息
Guys, great news.
我现在是本帮新的领袖啦
I'm the new leader of the gang!
马修和莉莉几乎把他们的新家布置妥当了
Marshall and Lily were almost done decorating their new home.
-放在这里好多了  -是啊
- I like it there much better. - Yeah.
但还有一个问题
There was only one problem.
不对
Wrong!
这个不能放这儿
This can't go here.
孩子们  当莉莉的古怪老爸
Kids, when he found out she was pregnant,
两周前
得知她怀孕后
Lily's estranged father
意外地出现在她家门口时
unexpectedly showed up on her doorstep.
莉莉深受感动
It was a gesture she appreciated.
可过了两周  他们就受不了了
But after two weeks, they'd had just about enough.
椅子必须放到那儿
That has to go there
好遮住那块开裂的地板
to cover up the splintery floorboard.
照片也不能挂这儿
And you can't hang this picture here.
这块不是石膏  只是干掉的牙膏
This isn't plaster; it's dried toothpaste.
幸好我在这儿
Guys, you're so lucky I'm here.
我就是在这房子里长大的
I grew up in this house.
对它可是了如指掌
I know it like the back of my hand.
这盏灯不能杵在这儿
And this lamp absolutely cannot be here.
为什么不能
Why not?
阻挡我偷窥寡妇罗德里格斯
Blocks my view of the Widow Rodriguez
做老年健身操的视线
doing her Jane Fonda workouts.
她有点太老了吧  爸爸
Isn't she a little old, Dad?
你眼中的她跟我小时候见的不一样
Oh, you didn't see her when I was a kid.
在我心里  她永远是五十四岁
In my mind, she'll always be 54.
我知道他是好意  但我再也受不了了
I know he means well, but I can't take it anymore.
他不会走的  他表现得
He won't leave, and-and he's acting
-就好像这里是他家  -对  我知道
- like this is his house. - No, I know.
而且他还到处留这些烦人的纸条
And these annoying notes he keeps leaving around?
"我练鼓的时候  需要绝对的安静"
"I need absolute silence when practicing the drums."
"不要碰我床头柜的软糖"
"Do not touch the fudge in my nightstand."
"我床头柜上需要防蚁"
"We need ant traps for my nightstand."
我发现自己老是躲在这里
I find myself hiding out here
就因为这里是这房子唯一一间
just because it's the only room in the house
他不会对我们指手画脚的房间
where he can't boss us around.
好消息
Great news.
我给以前的对讲机系统换了新电池
I put new batteries in the old intercom system.
这下我们可以随时沟通了
Now we can communicate at all times.
米奇通话完毕
Mickey out.
瞧瞧我们的卡座成了什么样子
Look at what's become of our booth.
就像我以前工艺课老师的手
Looks like my old shop teacher's hand--
会让人触景伤情欲罢不能
just sort of missing something.
够了
Enough!
我受够了你们俩在这儿唉声叹气
I am sick of you two wallowing in sadness,
还倒不如积极一点
instead of doing the healthy thing
假装那些离开你们的人
and pretending anyone who leaves you
从来没有出现过
never existed in the first place.
我很不想赞同巴尼这种
I hate to agree with Barney's
近乎自我麻痹的遗忘心理
near-paralyzing abandonment issues,
不过他说得有理
but he has a point.
不能因为朋友搬走了
You can't just stop living
你们就活不下去了吧
because two of your friends moved away.
非常正确
Precisely.
现在  作为团队的新领袖
Now, as new group leader,
我提议我们去做点
I say we go out and do something
马修和莉莉在时绝对不会去做的事
that we never would have done with Marshall and Lily here.
记得那次我想到一个绝妙的点子吗
Remember that amazing idea I had that one time?
-我们去脱衣舞俱乐部吧  -不要
- Let's go to a strip club. - Nope.
2005年的每天晚上
你们觉得怎么样
So what do you say?
让我们用一段"坐鸡起舞"
Let's declare our independence
来宣告我们的独立
with an on-da-peen dance.
"坐鸡起舞"是指...
On-the-peen dance.
-我们懂的  -我们了解
- No, we got it. - We got it.
我们去脱衣舞俱乐部吧
Let's go to a strip club!
这个嘛...
Well...
反正不管我到哪儿都会想他们
I'm going to miss them anywhere.
能边看大胸边想他们也不错
Might as well see some cans while I'm at it.
这事交给我吧
I'll take it!
罗宾  凯文  你们去吗
Robin, Kevin, you in?
孩子们  每一段恋爱的初期
Kids, early in any relationship,
都有一个让你凡事不忍拒绝的阶段
there's a phase where you don't say no to anything.
因为你想让自己看起来富有趣味
Because you want to seem interesting...
在中央公园看鸟
乐于冒险
adventurous...
蹦极
思想开放
and open-minded.
屠夫课程
我管它叫做恋爱早期懦弱症
I call it Early Relationship Chicken.
我乐于尝试任何事物
Well, I'm open to anything.
我也是
Oh, mos' def.
-那么...  -那么...
- So... - So...
我可不想去脱衣舞俱乐部
I don't want to go to a strip club.
我才不要去脱衣舞俱乐部
但我不想让他觉得我假正经
But I don't want him to think I'm some prude.
天啊  我们已经拖延好一会儿了
Man, we've been saying "So" for a while.
-好啊  -好啊
- Yeah! - Yeah!
太好了
Yes!
今晚将会成为传...
Tonight is going to be legen--
等等  我们肯定去脱衣舞俱乐部是个好主意吗
Wait, are we sure it's a good idea to go to a strip club?
闭嘴  莉莉  现在我说了算
Shut up, Lily! I'm in charge now
...奇
-dary!
我手机没信号
I've got no cell reception.
我想打给泰德
I wanted to call Ted.
这感觉真奇怪
This feels weird.
上次我住得离他这么远
The last time I lived this far from him
还是我去海外学习的时候
was my semester abroad.
你从没去海外学习过
You never did a semester abroad.
我把住在校园的两端两两相望  称为"海外学校"
That's what I called it when we lived on opposite sides of campus.
不对
Wrong!
告诉我你不是要把它插进去吧
Please tell me you're not plugging that in there.
没错  米奇  我正要这么做
Yes, Mickey, that's exactly what I'm doing.
好吧  可以  我不会有任何异议
All right, fine. I won't say anything.
只不过  我从小就住在这间房
It's... just that this was my room when I was growing up,
所以知道的要比你多一点
so I know it a little better than you.
这里充满美好回忆
Lot of great memories here.
大部分是关于"探索"我身体的奥秘
Mostly just discovering my body.
够了
That's it.
米奇  自从你搬进来
Mickey, since you got here,
就什么也看不惯  还自作主张
you've been nothing but judgmental and pushy
还过分沉溺于自己青春期的性生活
and strangely obsessed with your adolescent sex life.
明天早上
Tomorrow morning,
请你从这儿搬走
you're out of here.
我只是想帮助你们
Well, I-I've just been trying to help you...
我们不需要你帮
We don't need your help!
我...
I...
没事的  宝贝
Oh, it-it's okay, baby.
这话总得说出口
It had to be done.
真遗憾  唯一一个
Too bad the one person
能阻止你们犯这样错误的人
who could stop you from making mistakes like that
竟然被告知下个月必须搬走
was told he has to move out next month.
-是明天  -明天
- Tomorrow! - Tomorrow!
谁想请我跳支舞呀
Would either of you like a dance?
我随时准备摇头嗨起来
I'm always ready to rock.
我也随时准备晃脑爽起来
And I'm always ready to roll.
-那么...  -那么...
- So... - So...
我可没准备摇头
I'm not ready to rock.
晃脑会让我头晕眼花
Rolling makes me dizzy.
-管他呢  好啊  -太好了
- Hell, yeah! - Yeah!
我要为我的男人买一段膝上舞
I'm buying my man a lap dance,
女朋友就该这样
'cause that's just how I do!
尽情舞动吧
Party like a rock star!
Party like a rock star...
伙计们  我是泰德
Uh, hey, guys. It's Ted.
你们可能还在忙搬家的事
Um... you're probably busy with the move still.
如果你们想找人扯淡就给我回电
Give me a call if you want to gab.
抱歉用了"扯淡"这个字眼
Sorry about using the word "Gab."
泰德  别再因为马修和莉莉闷闷不乐了
Ted, stop pining over Marshall and Lily.
有点自尊心好不好
Have some self-respect.
快咬住这张五块钱  好让...
Now put this fiver in your mouth so...
那个眼神性感的舞娘吸出来...
that stripper with the lazy eye can vacuum it up with...
-巴尼  -干什么
- Barney! - Wh-what?
我总有权利想他们吧
I'm allowed to miss them, okay?
他们俩是我最好的朋友
They're my two best friends.
我才是你最好的朋友
I'm your two best friends!
而我今晚带你来这里
And we're here tonight
是为了让你知道  既然有更好的替代品
to show you there's no need to miss something
就没必要对以前的东西恋恋不舍了
when you can replace it with something better.
先生们  欢迎小茉莉出场
Gentlemen, say hello to J-J-J-Jasmine!
还记得她吗
Remember her?
两年前
之前我们发现了一件超棒的事
So, a while back, we discovered the most amazing thing:
莉莉有位酷似者
Lily had a doppelganger
那人是个俄国脱衣舞娘
who was a Russian stripper.
看看她  泰德
Look at her, Ted.
她就像年纪大点的蹩脚货莉莉
She's just like old, less-good Lily,
可她不会对我们发号施令
but instead of bossing us around,
反而会对我们"一泄春光"
she shows us her boobs.
不许碰
No touching.
好吧  还是会有点儿爱发号施令
Okay, a little bossing us around.
我管她叫升级版莉莉
I call her Better Lily.
升级版莉莉  请为我朋友跳支舞
Hey, Better Lily, please dance for my friend.
巴尼  我不需要膝上舞
Barney, I don't need a lap dance.
我要和我的朋友聊天
I need to talk to my friends.
谁说你不能鱼与熊掌兼得
Who says you can't do both?
和她聊啊  她又不是没耳朵
Talk to her. She's got ears.
没错  她的确有耳朵
Yes, she does have ears.
你想摸我女朋友的咪咪吗
You want to touch my girlfriend's boobs?
五十块
50 bucks.
等等  升级版莉莉在和这个巨兽交往
Wait-- Better Lily is dating this behemoth?
这形容词会不会让你想起某人
Sound like anyone you know?
那是全新版马修
That's New Marshall.
本帮人齐啦
This is our gang now.
伙计们  又是我  泰德
Hey, guys, Ted again.
我开始觉得你们把我遗忘了
Starting to think you forgot about me.
还是某个酷邻居抢走了我的地位
Or replaced me with some cool neighbor.
这小子叫什么名字
What's his name?!
我逗你们玩呢
I'm totally kidding.
不管怎样
Anyway, uh...
我在努力回忆你们的样子
just trying to remember what your faces look like.
泰德  在脱衣舞俱乐部喝酒时
Ted, when they serve alcohol at a strip club,
给我爷们点儿
you're not allowed to show your vagina.
朋友  只需一百  裙底风光一览无余
100 bucks, and you will see the world, my friend.
他们已经懒得接我电话了
They're already ignoring my calls?
听着  我这个人很现实
Look, I'm realistic.
我知道我不得不习惯一个人去看牙医
I knew I'd have to get used to going to the dentist alone,
但我还是不觉得他们会把我三振出局
but I didn't think they'd cut me out completely.
如果他们不需要我们  那我们也不需要他们
If they don't need us, we don't need them.
终于开窍了
Yes! Finally!
对了  你看到她是怎么开瓶的吗
By the way, did you see how she opened that bottle?
在郊区断电  屋里...可真暗啊
Lights out in the suburbs is... is really dark.
保险丝盒在哪里
Where's the fuse box?
不知道
I don't know.
我知道在哪里
I know where it is.
如果我没在忙着卷铺盖走人的话  或许能帮上忙
Maybe I could fix it for you, if I wasn't so busy packing.
好吧
You know what?
我猜保险丝盒在地下室
I bet the fuse box is in the basement.
我...我自己去找
I'll just... I'll go find it myself.
能有多费劲
How hard can it be?
hard有"费劲"和"坚硬"的意思
和你刚撞上的桌板一样坚硬
As hard as that desk you just walked into?
回击得好  米奇
Good burn, Mickey.
该奖励你一块床头柜里的软糖
You deserve a little nightstand fudge for that one.
我该看哪里
Where do I look?
我不能看她的胸部
I mean, I can't look at her chest.
该死  我刚看了
Damn it! I just did.
或许罗宾没注意到
Maybe Robin didn't notice.
天啊  他还真沉醉在那对大咪咪里了
Man, he's really up in those jugs.
动起来  宝贝
Shake it, baby!
好戏要上场了
A player's gotta play!
真奇怪
This is weird.
我还是看她的眼睛吧
I'll just look her in the eyes.
他难不成爱上这个脱衣舞娘了
Is he falling in love with this stripper?
快  要表现出无所谓
Quick, do something cool.
哥哥  好豪气呀
Make it rain, son!
老子不在乎钱
Money ain't no thang!
靠  里面有张二十块
Damn it, there was a 20 in there.
你好  埃里克森先生
Hello, Mr. Eriksen.
根据风铃声来判断
From the sound of the wind chimes,
你已经到了一楼
I hear you've made it to the first floor.
好吧  米奇
Okay... you know what, Mickey.
省省你恐怖游戏大师那套吧
You can save the creepy game master routine.
它只吓唬到我一丁点而已
It's only kind of terrifying me.
可游戏才刚开始
Oh, but the game has just begun.
我管它叫"马修  在去地下室修保险丝盒的路上
I call it "Try Not to Bang into All the Furniture and Stuff
要尽量避免撞上家具和杂物"
on Your Way to the Fuse Box in the Basement, Marshall."
这只是暂用名而已
That's just a working title.
你的眉毛上粘了咪咪亮粉  皮条客
Got a little boob glitter on your eyebrow, Mac Daddy.
人在江湖飘  那能不挨刀
Straight pimpin'.
巴尼  你脸上也有
Barney, you got a little bit, too.
哪里
Where?
弄下来了吗
Did I get it?
弄下来了
Yeah, you got it.
谁需要马修和莉莉
Who needs Marshall and Lily?
我们组建了新队伍
We got a new gang,
而且我们永不分离
and we're all going to hang out together forever.
我的钟点到了
My shift is done.
再见
Good-bye.
等等  别走
Wait, stop!
严格说来  这首曲子还没完  所以你还是我们的
Technically, this song's not over, so we still own you.
再说了  我们是最好的朋友
Plus we're best friends!
接下来去哪里
Where to next?
我们要去地下赌场玩扑克
We go to underground poker game
在一个近乎废弃的精神病院里
in mostly-abandoned insane asylum.
太好了
Yes!
肯定超好玩
This is gonna be awesome,
到时我要你们都记住
and when it is, I want you all to remember
带领你们去的人是在下  巴尼·斯丁森
who led you there: Barney Stinson,
团队的新领袖
new group leader.
你们的筹码都归我啦
I'm winning all your chippies!
这时候不许喝酒
Let's not drink when we're...
我口渴  没事
I'm thirsty; it's good.
没事的
It's good.
马修  我刚想起来垃圾箱旁的抽屉里
Marshall, I just remembered I saw a box of matches
有盒火柴
in the drawer by the trash can.
好  谢谢  宝贝
Okay, thanks, baby.
莉莉  我找不到
Lily, I can't find them.
在找这个吗
Looking for these?
对了  你看不到我
Oh, right, you can't see me.
我在烧你急需的火柴
Um, well, I'm burning the matches you so desperately need.
米奇  你猜谁找到通往地下室楼梯了
Mickey... guess who found the basement stairs?
我马上就下去找保险丝盒了
I'll be down at that fuse box in no time,
一旦我到那儿
and when I get there,
我肯定能摸清保险丝盒的工作原理
I'm sure that I'll figure out how fuse boxes work,
然后修好它
so it'll be fine.
马修
Hey, Marshall,
我知道我一直在混淆你的视听
I know I've been messing with you,
不过说真的  那第二级台阶  别...
but seriously, that second step, don't...
我不想听  米奇
I don't want to hear it, Mickey.
我的膝盖
Oh, my knee!
当心我的那套架子鼓
And watch out for my drum set.
我又赢了
I win again!
我刚在虚张声势
I was bluffing.
我甚至连牌数都不够
I didn't even have enough cards.
泰德  求你别再赢了
Ted, please stop winning.
看  这是纽约城的轮廓线
Hey, look, it's the New York City skyline.
* 建造筹码之城 *
* We built Chip City *
* 建造筹码之城  多得君之钱币 *
* We built Chip City on all your dough *
* 建造筹码之城  加油 *
* Built Chip City ? Hit it! *
跟你说  蝴蝶刀
You know butterfly knife.
我还以为那个"纹身脸"会先动手
I'd expect this from Face Tattoo...
或"歪嘴刀疤脸"
or Jagged Cheek Scar,
或拉里
or Larry,
但绝不是你
but not you.
我为什么没有外号
Why don't I get nickname?
因为你特征太多了  拉里
Because you have too many things, Larry.
只有一点才好取外号
You get one thing!
瞧  这就是你带全新版马修来的用处
See, that's why you bring New Marshall.
我们要去屠宰场参加派对
We go to party in slaughterhouse.
你们来吗
You come?
老天爷  我不想去啊
Please, God, no.
千万别再让我瞎指挥了
Don't let me be in charge of the gang anymore.
真不敢相信凯文医生居然忘了
I can't believe Dr. Kevin doesn't remember me
三年前给我做过心理辅导
from our sessions three years ago.
这不是刺伤了所有狱警的那个疯子吗
Is that the lunatic that stabbed all those prison guards?
我们必须参加那派对
We gotta hit that party!
我和真爱永远无缘了
I'll never find love.
我们必须参加那派对
We got to hit that party!
好耶
Sweet.
莉莉
Lily?
我觉得咱们不应该搬来郊外
I think we made a mistake moving out to the suburbs.
我想念我们的公寓
I miss our home.
我想念我们的卡座和我们的朋友
I miss our booth with our friends.
而且有个鼓槌正卡在我的
And I'm pretty sure I have a drumstick...
难言之处
somewhere bad.
爸爸  你为什么要这么做
Dad, why are you acting like this?
我只是想帮你们的忙
Well, I was just trying to be helpful,
可你们却要我在七月国庆节前搬走
but you guys want me out by the Fourth of July.
是明天就搬
Tomorrow.
你知道一个帮得上忙的父亲
You know what a helpful father,
或者是帮得上忙的姥爷会怎么做吗
not to mention grandfather, might do?
让这房子重获光明
Get these lights back on.
好吧  马修  听着
Okay, Marshall, listen up.
我将指引你找到那保险丝盒
I'm gonna get you to that fuse box.
求求你下来帮我把闸合上吧
Can't you just come down here and do it for me, please?
我对这房子一无所知
I don't know anything about this house.
不  马修
No, Marshall...
你是对你自己的房子一无所知
you don't know anything about your house.
行了  我们要干的事多着呢
All right, we got a lot of work to do.
在这里等着  我们去把你们弄进派对的"宾贵"名单
Wait here, we get you on VPI list for party.
你们每人就给  两百大洋吧
You give us, uh, $200 per person.
入场费嘛
Cover charge.
这入场费也太宰人了吧
That's pretty steep for a cover charge.
这派对可牛了
Is very good party.
主题是纽约"羊基队"和可口可乐
Is party for, uh, New York "Yunkees" and Coca-Cola.
两者皆为纽约常见事物
我的天
Oh, my God.
可口可乐和洋基队的派对吗
A Coca-Cola Yankees party?
感觉不像骗人
That sounds like a real thing.
好  马修  现在向前走三步
Okay, now, Marshall, take three steps forward,
同时注意低头躲开坏掉的吊扇
while ducking underneath the broken ceiling fan.
现在看向你的左侧
Now look to your left
吐一口口水
and spit.
那是热水器
That's the water heater.
离那玩意儿远点
Want to stay away from that.
它可比穿弹力紧身衣的寡妇罗德里格斯还要人命
That baby is hotter than the Widow Rodriguez in a unitard.
绕过洗衣机和烘干机是最难的部分
Okay, now past the washer and dryer is the hardest part.
你必须从乒乓球桌下匍匐前进
You're gonna have to belly-crawl underneath the ping-pong table
轻轻碰一下都不行
and don't so much as nudge it.
为什么
Why not?
因为上面放置了九百块
Because there are 900 dominos set up
美国老牌女影星  代表作《金发的珍妮》
摆成芭芭拉·伊登的多米诺骨牌
in the shape of Barbara Eden.
我是《金发的珍妮》的骨灰级粉丝
Big, big I Dream Of Jeannie fan.
我爬过去了
I'm clear.
我可不知道那是什么声音  米奇
I don't know what that sound is, Mickey.
那是我与芭芭拉·伊登性福无缘的声音
That's the sound of Barbara Eden never banging me.
美好祝愿分崩离析
That's what that is.
爸爸  快继续
Dad, get it back.
好  马修
Okay, Marshall,
向前走三步
take three steps forward,
就到保险丝盒处了
and you should be at the fuse box.
你觉得他成功了吗
Do you think he made it?
我成功了
I did it!
不  马修
No, Marshall...
是你成功了
you did it.
有趣的是  那一夜启发米奇创造出一个
Fun fact: that night inspired Mickey's one
并且是他唯一一个成功的桌面游戏
and only successful board game--
* 岌岌可危的地板  锈迹斑斑的铁钉 *
* With splintery floorboards and rusty nails *
* 危机四伏  步步惊心 *
* Make sure you don't get impaled *
* 拉灯 *
* Lites Out! *
艾得仁游戏倾情奉献
Brought to you by Aldrin Games!
从那位妓女接客的数目来判断
Well, judging from how many clients that hooker has serviced,
我们大概已等了一个小时了
I'd say we've been here almost an hour.
泰德  我们被人明抢了
Ted, we've been robbed.
升级版莉莉和全新版马修不会抢我们的
Better Lily and New Marshall would never rob us.
他俩是我们最好的朋友
They're our best friends.
冷静  各位
待会儿我要把这傻子洗劫一空
该死的  泰德
Damn it, Ted.
全新版马修就是只逃出动物园的大熊
New Marshall is an escaped zoo bear
而升级版莉莉唯一胜过我们莉莉的
and the only thing that Better Lily is better at than our Lily
就是她那手"隔裤摸鸡"的功夫
is over-the-pants hand stuff.
纯属猜测
I'm assuming.
我承认
I'll admit it.
这队伍我带不了
I can't lead this group.
我们需要马修和莉莉
We need Marshall and Lily.
但他们已经脱离队伍了  不是吗
But they're gone, aren't they?
咱们跟他们的碰面会从一周几次
I mean, it'll go from seeing them a couple times a week,
变成一个月几次
to a couple times a month,
接着要等逢年过节才能碰上一面
and then it'll just be holiday parties.
时光转瞬即逝
Then the years pass,
马修驾鹤西去
and you find out Marshall's dead,
起初你留下来安抚莉莉
and you're there for Lily emotionally at first,
然后安抚变成了爱抚  你深感愧疚
but then it becomes sexual, and you feel guilty,
但这愧疚却让欲火烧得更猛更烈
but maybe that guilt just makes it dirtier and better...
不  我不会让这一切发生的
No, I won't let that happen.
尤其是最后那部分
Especially that last part.
我知道今晚我有点醉  行为有点幼稚
Look, I know I've been a little drunk and naive tonight,
但我已经计划好了
but here's what's gonna happen.
首先  给升级版莉莉
First, we're gonna leave a note for Better Lily
-和阿维达斯留个条  免得他们担心  -伙计啊
- and Arvydas, they're worriers. - Oh, buddy.
立陶宛籍前NBA球员  身高2.21米
然后我们就去找独一马修和无二莉莉
Then, we're gonna go see Only Marshall and One-Of-A-Kind Lily
因为他俩是我们最好的朋友
because they're our best friends
而且仅需四十六分钟的车程
and they're only 46 minutes away.
跟我走不
Are you with me?
虽然不愿意被你夺权  不过我们出发吧
Kind of resent the power grab, but okay, let's go!
你想跟我们一起去长岛吗
Hey, do you want to come to Long Island with us?
这个嘛  离天亮倒是还有一段时间
Uh, well, still a few more hours before the sun comes up.
那么
So...
-不想  -不想
- No. - No?
这样是不是不好呀
Is that bad?
不  好得很
No, it's great.
太棒了
Ooh, that felt so good.
我就喜欢不做事家里蹲
I hate doing things and going anywhere!
尝试新事物最无聊了
Oh, new experiences suck!
说到这个  我讨厌跟你击掌
While we're at it, I hate high-fiving you!
我明白
I know.
我们是睡在一起的成年人
We're adults who are sleeping together,
又不是宣誓入会的青少年
not teens pledging a frat.
其实我挺喜欢击掌的
Oh, man, I really liked the high-five.
第二天早上  马修和莉莉一起床便迎来惊喜
The next morning, Marshall and Lily woke up to a surprise.
你们  你们怎么在这里
Hey, what are... what are you guys doing here?
来试下钥匙管不管用
Just wanted to make sure this key worked.
我们想你们
We missed you.
快让妈妈抱一个
Give mama a hug.
别听你的留言信箱
Don't check your voicemail.
里面也许有几通诡异留言
Y-You might have a couple weird ones.
你听见没
You hear this?!
这是我开始新生活的欢声
This is the sound of me moving on.
没错  我是个脱衣舞男
Yeah, I'm a stripper.
谁想吃薄煎饼
Okay, who wants pancakes?
你们哪两位想吃薄煎饼
Which two of you want pancakes?
我再多做几份
I'll make more.
太太太棒了  我要吃薄煎饼
Oh, good-good-good, 'cause I want pancakes.
拿去吧
There you go.
-多谢了  -没事
- Thank you. - Okay.
慢慢吃
Enjoy them.
亲爱的  听着
Hey, honey, look,
抱歉我之前如此惹人嫌
I'm sorry I was a jerk before.
吃完早饭我就走人
Okay? I'll leave right after breakfast.
我会暂住在朋友家
I'll crash with some friends.
爸爸
Dad, you know what?
留下来吧
You can stay.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
我一个朋友也没有
I got no friends.
我最多再呆两周
I'll be here two weeks, tops.
结果根本不止两周
It wasn't two weeks.
我们五人会永远住在离那个卡座
Would the five of us always live
数步之遥的地方吗
within a few minutes of that booth?
不  这就是生活  孩子们
No, that's life, kids,
但我发现
but here's what I discovered.
我们相聚在哪里  我们的卡座就在哪里
Our booth was wherever the five of us were together.
就是这样  寡妇罗德里格斯
That's right, Widow Rodriguez.
舒展开来
Stretch it.
抬起你的美腿
Work those gams.
握住你的左臂
Grab that left arm.
左臂发麻是心脏病发作症状之一
紧按你的胸口
Clutch that chest.
快速摔倒在地
Fall down really fast.
我的天啊  快打急救电话
Oh, my God! Somebody call 911!